// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let questions = [

    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "which of the following has No units",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "poissoris ratio",
      "strain",
      "Relative Permeability",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If the unit of mass is   0.5 kg, the unit of length is 2m and the unit of time is, then they unit of pressure is",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "0.25nm²",
      "2.5nm–²",
      "25nm–²",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Two Equal forces acting at a point have the Resultant equal to one of its force then the angle between two forces______",
    answer: "120°",
    options: [
      "45°",
      "30°",
      "120°",
      "60°"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The Maximum and minimum Resultant of two forces are in the Ratio 7:3. Then the Ratio of forces is",
    answer: "5:2",
    options: [
      "7:3",
      "√7:√3",
      "5:2",
      "49:9"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A body projected from the top of a tower with an initial velocity 30m/s hits the ground at an angle 30°.the vertical component of velocity at the time of hitting will be",
    answer: "17m/s",
    options: [
      "10m/s",
      "17m/s",
      "30m/s",
      "om/s"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A body of man 1kg is moving towards cart with a uniform speed of 2m/s a force of 2N is applied to it towards the north Magnitude of the displacement of the body 2s after the force is applied is____",
    answer: "4√2m",
    options: [
      "8√2m",
      "8m",
      "4√2m",
      "4m"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A particle starts from the original t=0 and moves in the plan with the constant acceleration α in the y direction its equation of motion is y=βx². its velocity in the x direction is",
    answer: "√α/2β",
    options: [
      "α/β",
      "2α/β",
      "√α/2β",
      "√2α/β"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "for the same range two heights attained are 20 m & 80m the range is",
    answer: "160m",
    options: [
      "120m",
      "20m",
      "40m",
      "160m"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "from a place where g=9.8m/sec²,a stone is thrown upwards with a 4.9 m/sec. The time taken for the stone to return to the earth is",
    answer: "1sec",
    options: [
      "2sec",
      "1sec",
      "4sec",
      "8sec"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If a splash is heard 4.23 sec afta a stone is dropped into a well 78.4m deep, then the velocity of sound is",
    answer: "340m/sec",
    options: [
      "3x10⁸m/sec",
      "340m/sec",
      "354m/sec",
      "300m/sec"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The acceleration of a simple harmonic Oscillator is 1ms–², when its displacement from mean position is 0.5m. Then its frequency of oscillation is",
    answer: "1/√2π Hz",
    options: [
      "√2π Hz",
      "π/√2 Hz",
      "1/√2π Hz",
      "√2/π Hz"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The velocity of a body executing SHM at the Mean Position is numerically equal to the acceleration at the extreme position.then the period of oscillation is",
    answer: "2π",
    options: [
      "π",
      "2π",
      "π²",
      "4π²"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "when a man m is suspended from spring its frequency of oscillations is n. if an additional man 3m is attached,its frequency is n2,then n2/n1  [",
    answer: "½",
    options: [
      "½",
      "2",
      "4",
      "¼"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "if the absorption changes by 2%, then the percentage change in the Reverberation time is___",
    answer: "2%",
    options: [
      "1%",
      "2%",
      "3%",
      "4%"
    ]
  }, 
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "A gas at 27°c and pressure 30 atmosphere is allowed to expand to atmospheric pressure and Volume 15times larger. calculate the final temparatore of the gas",
    answer: "-123°c",
    options: [
      "-123°c",
      "173°c",
      "272°c",
      "None"
    ]
  }, 
];
